# Justin Ng

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

London United Kingdom +(44) 7794 028 673 justinng878@gmail.com

## Links

LinkedIn

**Github** 

My Portfolio

## Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Responsive Design

React

Version Control (Git and Github)

**Paired Programming** 

Working with RESTful API's

Website Accessibility Requirements

Effective Time Management

Communication

Route Planning

### Web Developer Profile

I am a web developer with experience in building projects using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. My background includes working on a data collection project for Google maps and I also have some experience in hospitality. From these roles I was able to develop other soft skills that are transferable to the role of a front-end developer including teamwork, collaboration and strong communication.

#### **Recent Projects**

### Gif me some exercises!

<u>LIVE</u> | <u>REPO</u> - A web application that displays different exercises dependent on the user's search. The user is able to look up exercises that target a specific body part or require a particular piece of equipment.

- This project demonstrates a strong understanding of the React library and utilises API documentation.

#### **Choose Your Pokemon!**

 $\underline{\sf LIVE}$  /  $\underline{\sf REPO}$  - A website application that allows the user to select a Pokemon and experience a battle style simulation against a computer.

- A collaborative project that introduces the use of JavaScript to add functionality to an app. In addition, this projects also utilises API documentation.

#### **Education and training**

## Web Development Bootcamp, Juno College of Technology, Toronto

SEPTEMBER 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

A 12 week immersive boot camp experience learning the fundamentals of front end development. Students were expected to produce 4 projects during the course to demonstrate the skills they had learned throughout.

#### German Studies, University of Warwick, Coventry

OCTOBER 2015 - MAY 2019

B.A (With Honours)

## **Employment History**

## Data Collector at TSMG Holding, London

MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

- Collaborated with a remote team for 15 months with aims to enrich the experience of Google search users through highly effective operations by providing accurate Geo Data information.
- Travelled to different locations and businesses every week and collected locations scans in order to improve the accuracy of Google location services.

## Customer Service Representative at Papayaya Bromley, London

MAY 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Worked within a small team of waiters to provide attentive customer service during lunch and dinner services, all in accordance with exceptional health and safety standards by maintaining very high levels of cleanliness.
- Provided efficient restaurant service by taking orders over the phone and through the restaurant ordering system, ensuring each individual customer received their correct order in a efficient manner.